<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pack CLI on Cloud Native Buildpacks</title>
    <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pack CLI on Cloud Native Buildpacks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pack</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack/</guid>
      <description>pack CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks
Synopsis CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks
Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;pack&#39; --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output --version Show current &#39;pack&#39; version SEE ALSO  pack build	- Generate app image from source code pack completion	- Outputs completion script location pack create-builder	- Create builder image pack inspect-builder	- Show information about a builder pack inspect-image	- Show information about a built image pack list-trusted-builders	- List Trusted Builders pack package-buildpack	- Package buildpack in OCI format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack build</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_build/</guid>
      <description>pack build Generate app image from source code
Synopsis Generate app image from source code
pack build &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -B, --builder string Builder image (default &amp;quot;cnbs/sample-builder:bionic&amp;quot;) -b, --buildpack strings Buildpack reference in the form of &#39;&amp;lt;buildpack&amp;gt;@&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;&#39;, path to a buildpack directory (not supported on Windows), path/URL to a buildpack .tar or .tgz file, or the name of a packaged buildpack image Repeat for each buildpack in order, or supply once by comma-separated list --clear-cache Clear image&#39;s associated cache before building -D, --default-process string Set the default process type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack completion</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_completion/</guid>
      <description>pack completion Outputs completion script location
Synopsis Generates bash completion script and outputs its location.
To configure your bash shell to load completions for each session, add the following to your &amp;lsquo;.bashrc&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;.bash_profile&amp;rsquo;:
. $(pack completion)  To configure your zsh shell to load completions for each session, add the following to your &amp;lsquo;.zshrc&amp;rsquo;:
. $(pack completion --shell zsh)  pack completion [flags] Options  -h, --help help for completion -s, --shell string Generates completion file for [bash|zsh] (default &amp;quot;bash&amp;quot;) Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack create-builder</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_create-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_create-builder/</guid>
      <description>pack create-builder Create builder image
Synopsis Create builder image
pack create-builder &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; --config &amp;lt;builder-config-path&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -c, --config string Path to builder TOML file (required) -h, --help Help for &#39;create-builder&#39; --publish Publish to registry --pull-policy string Pull policy to use. Accepted values are always, never, and if-not-present. The default is always Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack inspect-builder</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_inspect-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_inspect-builder/</guid>
      <description>pack inspect-builder Show information about a builder
Synopsis Show information about a builder
pack inspect-builder &amp;lt;builder-image-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -d, --depth int Max depth to display for Detection Order. Omission of this flag or values &amp;lt; 0 will display the entire tree. (default -1) -h, --help Help for &#39;inspect-builder&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack inspect-image</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_inspect-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_inspect-image/</guid>
      <description>pack inspect-image Show information about a built image
Synopsis Show information about a built image
pack inspect-image &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  --bom print bill of materials -h, --help Help for &#39;inspect-image&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack list-trusted-builders</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_list-trusted-builders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_list-trusted-builders/</guid>
      <description>pack list-trusted-builders List Trusted Builders
Synopsis List Trusted Builders.
Show the builders that are either trusted by default or have been explicitly trusted locally using trust-builder
pack list-trusted-builders [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;list-trusted-builders&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack package-buildpack</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_package-buildpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_package-buildpack/</guid>
      <description>pack package-buildpack Package buildpack in OCI format.
Synopsis Package buildpack in OCI format.
pack package-buildpack &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; --config &amp;lt;package-config-path&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -c, --config string Path to package TOML config (required) -f, --format string Format to save package as (&amp;quot;image&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;file&amp;quot;) -h, --help Help for &#39;package-buildpack&#39; --publish Publish to registry (applies to &amp;quot;--image&amp;quot; only) --pull-policy string Pull policy to use. Accepted values are always, never, and if-not-present. The default is always Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack rebase</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_rebase/</guid>
      <description>pack rebase Rebase app image with latest run image
Synopsis Rebase app image with latest run image
pack rebase &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;rebase&#39; --publish Publish to registry --pull-policy string Pull policy to use. Accepted values are always, never, and if-not-present. The default is always --run-image string Run image to use for rebasing Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack report</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_report/</guid>
      <description>pack report Display useful information for reporting an issue
Synopsis Display useful information for reporting an issue
pack report [flags] Options  -e, --explicit Print config without redacting information -h, --help Help for &#39;report&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack set-default-builder</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_set-default-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_set-default-builder/</guid>
      <description>pack set-default-builder Set default builder used by other commands
Synopsis Set default builder used by other commands.
** For suggested builders simply leave builder name empty. **
pack set-default-builder &amp;lt;builder-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;set-default-builder&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack set-run-image-mirrors</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_set-run-image-mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_set-run-image-mirrors/</guid>
      <description>pack set-run-image-mirrors Set mirrors to other repositories for a given run image
Synopsis Set mirrors to other repositories for a given run image
pack set-run-image-mirrors &amp;lt;run-image-name&amp;gt; --mirror &amp;lt;run-image-mirror&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;set-run-image-mirrors&#39; -m, --mirror strings Run image mirror Repeat for each mirror in order, or supply once by comma-separated list Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack suggest-builders</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_suggest-builders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_suggest-builders/</guid>
      <description>pack suggest-builders Display list of recommended builders
Synopsis Display list of recommended builders
pack suggest-builders [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;suggest-builders&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack suggest-stacks</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_suggest-stacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_suggest-stacks/</guid>
      <description>pack suggest-stacks Display list of recommended stacks
Synopsis Display list of recommended stacks
pack suggest-stacks [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;suggest-stacks&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack trust-builder</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_trust-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_trust-builder/</guid>
      <description>pack trust-builder Trust builder
Synopsis Trust builder.
When building with this builder, all lifecycle phases will be run in a single container using the builder image.
pack trust-builder &amp;lt;builder-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;trust-builder&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack untrust-builder</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_untrust-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_untrust-builder/</guid>
      <description>pack untrust-builder Stop trusting builder
Synopsis Stop trusting builder.
When building with this builder, all lifecycle phases will be no longer be run in a single container using the builder image.
pack untrust-builder &amp;lt;builder-name&amp;gt; [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;untrust-builder&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pack version</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/pack/pack_version/</guid>
      <description>pack version Show current &amp;lsquo;pack&amp;rsquo; version
Synopsis Show current &amp;lsquo;pack&amp;rsquo; version
pack version [flags] Options  -h, --help Help for &#39;version&#39; Options inherited from parent commands  --no-color Disable color output -q, --quiet Show less output --timestamps Enable timestamps in output -v, --verbose Show more output SEE ALSO  pack	- CLI for building apps using Cloud Native Buildpacks  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>