<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Cloud Native Buildpack Documentation</title>
    <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Cloud Native Buildpack Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buildpack API</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/buildpack-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/buildpack-api/</guid>
      <description>This specification defines the interface between a buildpack and the environment that runs it. This API will be used by buildpack authors.
A buildpack must contain three files:
 buildpack.toml bin/detect bin/build  The two files in bin/ must be executable. They can be shell scripts written in a language like Bash or they can be executables compiled from a language like Go.
bin/detect Usage bin/detect PLATFORM_DIR BUILD_PLAN Summary This entrypoint is used to determine if a buildpack should run against a given codebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distribution API</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/distribution-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/distribution-api/</guid>
      <description>This specification defines the artifact format, delivery mechanism, and order resolution process for buildpacks.
Buildpack Descriptor A buildpack must contain a buildpack.toml file in its root directory.
Buildpackage A buildpackage is a distributable artifact that contains a buildpack. Its format may be either:
 An OCI image An uncompressed tar archive with the extension .cnb containing an OCI image.  Further Reading You can read the complete Distribution specification on Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform API</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/platform-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/platform-api/</guid>
      <description>This specification defines the interface between the buildpack execution environment, referred to as the lifecycle, and a platform that supports it. This API is used by platform implementors.
Stacks A stack defines two OCI images: a build image and a run image. The build image is used to run the buildpack lifecycle, and the run image is the base image the final exported image will be built upon.
For more information see Working with stacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>builder.toml</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/builder-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/builder-config/</guid>
      <description>A builder configuration schema is as follows:
  description (string, optional) A human-readable description of the builder, to be shown in inspect-builder output (run pack inspect-builder -h for more information).
  buildpacks (list, optional) A list of buildpacks, each with the following fields:
  id (string, optional)
An identifier for the buildpack. Must match ID specified in buildpack&amp;rsquo;s buildpack.toml file.
  version (string, optional)
The version of the buildpack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>package.toml</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/package-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/package-config/</guid>
      <description>A buildpackage configuration schema is as follows:
  buildpack (required) The buildpack to package. It must contain the following field:
 uri (string, required)
A URL or path to an archive, or a path to a directory. If path is relative, it must be relative to the package.toml.    dependencies (list, optional) A set of dependent buildpack locations, for packaging a meta-buildpack. Each dependent buildpack location must correspond to an order group within the meta-buildpack being packaged, and must have one of the following fields:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible Builds</title>
      <link>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/reproducibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buildpacks.io/docs/reference/reproducibility/</guid>
      <description>Summary The Cloud Native Buildpacks project aims to create &amp;ldquo;Reproducible Builds&amp;rdquo; of container images. For image creation commands (create-builder, package-buildpack, build) pack creates container images in a reproducible fashion. &amp;ldquo;Reproducible&amp;rdquo; is hard to define but we&amp;rsquo;ll do so by example and with a few caveats:
Examples  Running pack build sample-hello-moon:test multiple times produces a container image with the same image ID (local case)
Given:
 The same source code The same builder image The same set of buildpacks (see caveat below).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>